Finding Aid for Michigan Schoolmasters' Club(University of Michigan) publications, 1895-1969
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Michigan Schoolmasters' Club (University of Michigan) publications 1895-1969
University of Michigan. Michigan Schoolmasters' Club.
1.5 linear ft.
97111 Bimu N201 2
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Publications are received periodically from the unit(Donor # 4808 ).
Periodic additions to the records expected.
The records are open to research.
The Publications of the Michigan Schoolmasters' Club primarily includes publications relating to the annual meeting of the group. Also included is a history and a list of books for high school students.
Subjects:
Michigan Schoolmasters' Club.
Genre Terms:
Bibliographies.; Histories.; Proceedings.; Programs.; Reports.
- Unit Publications
  - Catalogs
    - List of Books Recommended for a High School Classical Library, 1897 (Box 1)
  - Flyers, 1968 (Box 1)
  - Histories
    - A Story of the First Seven Decades, 1880-1957 1958 (Box 1)
  - Proceedings
    - Annual Meeting
      - First, 1886 (Box 1)
      - 1898-1966/67, 6 folders (Box 1)
        (Journal, 1907-1967)
    - Business Meetings, 1903-1935 (Box 2)
      - Report of the Third Meeting of the Mathematical Conference of the Michigan Schoolmasters' Club, 1896 (Box 2)
  - Programs
    - Annual Meeting
      - 1895-1969, 6 folders (Box 2)
    - Concert, 1923 (Box 2)
    - Education for National Unity (Box 2)
  - Reports
    - Physics: Suggestions for Laboratory Work, 1895 (Box 2)